Guide to the Stanford University, W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- RESEARCH ON ELECTRON SCATTERING AND NUCLEAR STRUCTURE
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 18 (600)-646), June 1957 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- THEORETICAL AND EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATION OF KLYSTRON
  - Contract, (AF 19 (604)-1065), March 1954 - December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- RESEARCH DIRECTED TOWARD GENERAL STUDIES IN HIGH-POWER BEAM TUBES
  - Contract and Amendments from June 16, 1955 through September 15, 1956, (AF19 (604)-1494), June 1955 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 19 (604)-1494), July 1955 - November 1956 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to Extend to March 31, 1957, (AF 19 (604)-1494), November 1956 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Extension Proposal with Increase in Total Estimated Cost to November 15, 1957 (AF 19 (604)-1494) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Extension Proposal Extending Date to November 15, 1956 (AF 19 (604)-1494) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Proposal for Increased Effort May 15 to November 15, 1956 with Increase in Total Cost, (AF 19 (604)-1494), May 1956 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Original Proposal, (AF 19 (604)-1494), April 1955 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Preliminary Draft - Original Proposal, (AF 19 (604)-1494), March 1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Requirements, Outline of Research Reports, etc., (AF 19 (604)-1494), July 1954, July 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Status Reports and Material, (AF 19(604)-1494), April 1957 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Budget, (AF 19 (604)-1494), June 1955 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Final Patent Certification, (AF 19 (604)-1494), June 1957 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory (Initial), (AF 19 (604)-1494), June 1956 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Termination Papers, (AF 19 (604)-1494), April 1957 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 19 (604)-1494), May 1957 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- BIOLOGICAL INVESTIGATION USING MAGNETIC RESONANCE METHODS
  - Contract and Amendments from July 1, 1955 through June 30, 1956, (AF 18 (600)-1511), July 1955 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 18 (600)-1511), September 1955 - December 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Extension Proposal for 1959 to 1960, (AF 18 (600)-1511), December 1958 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Proposal to AFOSR for Extension of AF 18(600)-1511 for Magnetic Resonance Methods(AF 18(600)-1511) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Proposal to AFOSR for Extension of AF 18(600)-1511 for Biological Investigations Using Magnetic Resonance Methods, (AF 18(600)-1511), March 1958 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 18 (600)-1511), August 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 18 (600)-1511), March 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Original Proposal, (AF 18 (600)-1511), April 1955 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for Same Research Submitted to AEC and Withdrawn, (AF 18 (600)-1511), March 1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Requirements, Outline of Reports, etc., (AF 18 (600)-1511), July 1955 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Patent Certification, (AF18(600)-1511), August 1960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 18 (600)-1511), June 1, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 18 (600)-1511), June 1, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Physical Inventories of Plant Equipment, (AF 18 (600)-1511), June 1, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Annual Physical Inventory, (AF 18 (600)-1511), June 1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory (Initial), (AF 18 (600)-1511), June 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Final Report, (AF 18 (600)-1511), October 1960 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 18 (600)-1511), October 1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- ESTABLISHMENT OF FUNDS FOR MICROWAVE LAB
  - Establishment of Funds for Microwave Lab, (Air Force No. 1), July 1955 - August 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- PRECISION METHOD OF MEASURING VELOCITY OF LIGHT
  - Contract and Amendments, (AF 18 (600)-1593), December 1955 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 18 (600)-1593, January 1956 - July 1957 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Memo re: Requirements, etc., (AF 18 (600)-1593), January 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - ARDC (OSR) - Proposal for Measuring Velocity of Light (AF 18 (600)-1593) (Box 16, Folder 23)
- PROJECT 1030: DEVELOPMENT OF HIGH POWER TWT AND HYBRID TUBES
  - Contract and Amendments, (AF 19 (604)-1924), July 1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Reports, Memos, etc., (AF 19 (604)-1924), August 1956 - May 1960 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Tentative Proposal for Continuation, (AF 19 (604)-1924), October 1957 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Modification, (AF 19 (604)-1924), February 1957, September 1957 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Proposal (Project 1030), (AF19 (604)-1924), May 1956 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Physical Inventories of Plant Equipment, (AF 19 (604)-1924), June 1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (AF 19 (604)-1924), June 1958 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Termination Papers, (AF19(604)-1924), October 1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Transfer of Final Property Accounting (Minor, Special Tooling, and Expendable), (AF 19 (604)-1924), April 1960 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 19 (604)-1924), August 1958 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- GENERAL STUDIES IN HIGH-POWER BEAM TUBES
  - Contract and Amendments, (AF 19 (604)-1930), April 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 19 (604)-1930), April 1962 - January 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Extension Proposal for General Studies in High Power Microwave Concepts from April 1, 1961 through March 31, 1962 - Chodorow, (AF 19 (604)-1930), December 1960 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Extension Proposal for April 1, 1960 through March 31, 1961, (AF19(604)-1930), November 1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Extension Proposal for April 1, 1959 through March 31, 1960, (AF19(604)-1930), December 1958 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to Extend Contract with Additional Cost for April 1, 1958 through March 31, 1959, (AF 19 (604)-1930), January 1958 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Tentative Proposal to Extend Contract, (AF 19 (604)-1930), October 1957 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - First Year Proposal (originally AF 1949 Extension Proposal), (AF 19 (604)-1930), July 1956 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Reports and Memos, (AF 19 (604)-1930), May 1957 - February 1962 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Minor Equipment and Special Tooling Transferred from Contract AF 19 (604)-5226, (AF 19 (604)-1930), October 1961 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Property Transfers from AF 33 (600)-27784, (AF 19 (604)-1930), March 1960 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Transfers from AF 33 (600)-27784 ERL, (AF 19 (604)-1930), January 1960 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Transfer of Final Inventory from Contract AF 19 (604)-1494, (AF 19 (604)-1930), June 1957 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Information on Auditors' Questions Regarding Final Billing, (AF 19 (604)-1930), August 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 19 (604)-1930), December 31, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 19 (604)-1930), June 1, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 19 (604)-1930), June 1, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Physical Inventories of Plant Equípment, (AF 19 (604)-1930), June 1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 19 (604)-1930), November 1962 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- THEORETICAL RESEARCH IN STATISTICAL MECHANICS
  - Theoretical Research in Statistical Mechanics, (AF 49 (638)-342), March 1958 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 49 (638)-342), August 1960 - February 1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - General, (AF 49 (638)-342), November 1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for Program of Research on Electro-Dynamic Problems of Astrophysics - Sturrock, (AF 49 (638)-342), April 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 49 (638)-342), May 1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 49 (638)-342), November 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Original Proposal, December 1957 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 49 (638)-342), December 31, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Initial Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (AF 49 (638)-342), June 1956 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 49 (638)-342), June 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- RESEARCH ON INTERACTION OF MICROWAVES WITH MATTER
  - Contract and Amendments, (AF 49(638)-415), May 1958 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 49 (638)-415), August 1959 - August 1962 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Extension Proposal for Interaction of Microwaves with Matter for May 1, 1962 through April 30, 1963 - Chodorow, (AF49 (638)-415), September 1961 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Extension Proposal for Interaction of Microwaves with Matter for May 1, 1961 through April 30, 1962 - Chodorow, (AF49 (638)-415), December 1960 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 49 (638)-415), February 1960 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 49 (638)-415), July 1959 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Original Proposal, (AF 49 (638)-415), January 1958 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 49 (638)-415), December 31, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 49 (638)-415), June 1, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Initial Annual Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 49 (638)-415), June 1, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Final Property Inventory, (AF 49 (638)-415), June 1962 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- INVESTIGATION OF MULTI-MEGAWATT BROADBAND MICROWAVE TUBES
  - Rome Air Development Center, (AF 30 (602)-1844), June 1958 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 30 (602)-1844), June 1958 - February 1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Extension Proposal for July 1, 1961 through June 30, 1962, (AF 30 (602)-1844), January 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Extension Proposal for July 1, 1961 through June 30, 1962, Ditto masters and extra copies. (AF 30 (602)-1844), Jan-61 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF 30 (602)-1844), April 1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF30(602)-1844), December 1958 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Proposal copies, (AF 30 (602)-1844), December 1957 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Government Furnished Equipment (GFE) - Hayes Furnace Shipment, (AF 30 (602)-1844), September 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Capital Equipment Expenditures, (AF 30 (602)-1844), April 1960 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Transfer of Final Inventory from Contract, (AF 30 (602)-1844), October 1958 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 30 (602)-1844), June 1, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 30 (602)-1844), June 1, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 30 (602)-1844), October 1961 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- RESEARCH DIRECTED TOWARD AN INVESTIGATION OF THE MICROWAVE PROPERTIES OF PLASMAS
  - Master Contract, (AF 19 (604)-5226), February 1959 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, (AF 19 (604)-5226), February 1959 - February 1962 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Extension Proposal, (AF19 (604)-5226), January 1960 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Original Proposal, (AF 19 (604)-5226), June 1958 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 19 (604)-5226), June 1, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 19 (604)-5226), March 1961 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- THEORETICAL AND EXPERIMENTAL MASER RESEARCH
  - Master Contract, (AF 49 (638)-660), May 1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 49 (638)-660), May 1959 - September 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Theoretical Study of Maser Work by E.T. Jaynes, (AF 49 (638)-660), February 1959 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Reports, (AF 49 (638)-660), May 1959 - May 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- RESEARCH ON PLASMA BOUNDARY STUDIES
  - Contract, (AF 33 (616)-8121), March 1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, AF 33 (616)-8121), January 1961 - August 1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Extension Proposal for March 1, 1964 through October 31, 1964, prepared and submitted by SEL in (AF 33 (616)-8121), January, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Extension Proposal for March 1, 1963 through February 28, 1964, (AF 33 (616)-8121), January 1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Extension Proposal for March 1, 1962 through February 28, 1963, (AF 33 (616)-8121), January 1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Original Proposal, (AF33 (616)-8121), December 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 33 (616)-8121), December 1962 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 33 (616)-8121), May 31, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 33 (616)-8121), December 31, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 33 (616)-8121), April 1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- MULTIMEGAWATT BROADBAND MICROWAVE TUBES
  - Contract, (AF 30 (602)-2575), September 1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 30 (602)-2575), October 1957 - August 1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Multimegawatt Broadband Microwave Tubes, (AF 30 (602)-2575), June 1963 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Multimegawatt Broadband Microwave Tubes, (AF 30 (602)-2575), June 1963 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Continuation Proposal for Multimegawatt Broadband Microwave Tubes by Chodorow for November 1, 1963 through October 31, 1964, (AF 30 (602)-2575), June 1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Continuation Proposal for Multimegawatt Broadband Microwave Tubes by Chodorow and Craig for September 1, 1962 through August 31, 1962, (AF 30 (602)-2575), June 1962 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Request for No-Cost Extension for September through October 31, 1962, (AF 30 (602)-2575), August 1962 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Proposal to RADC (Replacement for Contract AF 30 (602)-1844) for September 1, 1961 through August 31, 1962, (AF 30 (602)-2575), July 1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Transfer of Property from AF 30 (602)-1844, (AF 30 (602)-2575), August 1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Transfer of Property from AF 30 (602)-3098, (AF 30 (602)-2575), November, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 30 (602)-2575), December 1962 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 30 (602)-2575), May 1962 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 30 (602)-2575), December 1961 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 30 (602)-2575), May 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- PRODUCTION AND INVESTIGATION OF HIGHLY IONIZED PLASMA (SECRET)
  - Contract, (AF 30 (602)-2490), November 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 30 (602)-2490), March 1962 - April 1964 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - No-Cost Extension for Contract for November 1, 1962 through December 31, 1962, (AF 30 (602)-2490), November 1962 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Original Proposal for A Study of the Microwave Properties of Cesium Plasmas, (AF 30 (602)-2490), April 1961 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Transfer of Minor Equipment, Special Tooling, and Expendables from AF 30 (602)-2490 to AF 30 (602)-3490, (AF 30 (602)-2490), March 1961 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AF 30 (602)-2490), December 31, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 30 (602)-2490), March 1963 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- RESEARCH ON SELECTED MICROWAVE PROPERTIES OF FERRITES
  - Contract, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), February 1962 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), July 1962 - September 1965 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Continuation Proposal on Research on Selected Microwave Properties of Ferrites, by Shaw, for April 1, 1964 through March 31, 1965, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), November 1963 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Extension of Research on Selected Microwave Properties of Ferrites for April 1, 1963 through March 31, 1964, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), November 1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Research Area of Interest on the Microwave Properties of Ferrites, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), December 1961 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Proposal for Research on the Microwave Properties of Ferrites, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), December 1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Internal Memorandum Linear Excitation of Magnetoelastic Waves in a Ferrite, by Shaw, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), February 1963 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Transfer of Property from AF 19 (604)-1930, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), March 1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Property Inventory, (AF 19 (628)-342CR), July 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- INTERACTION OF MICROWAVES WITH MATTER
  - Grant Instrument and Research Grant Advice, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-343), May 1962 - July 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-343), June 1962 - January 1964 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for Continued Support of Interaction of Microwaves with Matter by Chodorow and Shaw, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-343), June 1962 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Final Patent Certification and Final Technical Report, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-343), May 1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- PROBLEMS OF ASTROPHYSICS
  - Electrodynamic Problems of Astrophysics by Sturrock, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-326), December 1962 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for Continued Support, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-326), March 1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for Continuation for July 30, 1962 through June 30, 1963, (AF Grant AFOSR 62-326), April 1960 - February 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- INTERACTION OF MICROWAVES WITH MATTER
  - Grant Instrument and Research Grant Advice, (AF Grant AFOSR 322-63), May 1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, (AF Grant AFOSR 322-63), April 1963 - December 1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- THERMAL PLASMA INVESTIGATION
  - Contract, (AF 30 (602)-3098), March 1963 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 30 (602)-3098), May 1963 - October 1966 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Proposal to RADC for A Study of the Microwave Properties of Cesium Plasmas by Kino, (AF 30 (602)-3098), March 1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Contract Termination, (AF 30 (602)-3098), May 1964 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AF 30 (602)-3098), May 1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- OPTICAL MASER AND COHERENT PLASMA STUDIES
  - (AF Grant AFOSR 323-63), May 1963 - May 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Termination, (AF Grant AFOSR 323-63), September 1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- CONFIDENTIAL
  - Contract, (DA 44-009 eng-795), June 1951 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, (DA 44-009 eng-795), July 1952 - May 1954 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Security Clearance, (DA 44-009 eng-795), June 1951 - July 1957 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Requests for Approval, (DA 44-009 eng-795), July 1951 - August 1953 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Property Records, (DA 44-009 eng-795), October 1952 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Final Property Accounting, (DA 44-009 eng-795), December 1953 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- MOLECULAR OSCILLATOR STUDY
  - Contract and Amendments, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), March 1956 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), March 1956 - September 1959 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Request for Extension, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), March 1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Extension Proposal for November 1, 1956 through November 1, 1957, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), November 1956 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Signal Corps - Revised Proposal for Molecular Oscillator, (DA378 (039) SC-71178), November 1955 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for Molecular Oscillator, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), September 1955 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Reports and Memos, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), March 1956 - October 1957 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), June 1957 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Termination, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), October 1958 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Final Property Accounting, (DA 378 (039) SC-71178), October 1958 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- RADIATION FROM RELATIVISTIC ELECTRONS
  - Contract and Amendments, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), June 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), July 1956 - October 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Extension Proposal for September 15 - November 30, 1959 and December 1, 1959 through June 30, 1960 (DA 36 (039) SC-72785) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Extension Proposal, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), June 1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Revised Proposal to Signal Corps for Supplemental Agreement to Contract, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), March 1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Extension Proposal for December 14, 1957 through December 14, 1958 (DA 36 (039) SC-72785) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Proposal (Sub-millimeter waves), (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), March 1956 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Reports, Memos, etc., (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), October 1956 - July 1957 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Patent Certification and other Matters Pertaining to Termination, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), December 1960 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Transfer of Final Inventory from Contract DA 36 (039) SC-63180, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), March 1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Annual Interim Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), February 1960 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Annual Interim Physical Inventory of Equipment, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), June 1958 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Initial Annual Physical Inventory, (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), June 1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Final Property and Accounting (Location and Description), (DA 36 (039) SC-72785), October 1960 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- ESTABLISHMENT OF FUNDS FOR MICROWAVE LABORATORY
  - Establishment of Funds for Microwave Laboratory, (Signal Corps No. 2), September 1955 - September 1956 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- ESTABLISHMENT OF FUNDS FOR RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT IN THE FIELD OF MICROWAVE TUBES AND DEVICES
  - Signal Corps No. 3, March 1957 - September 1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- SOLID STATE TWO LEVEL HIGH POWER MASER
  - Contract, (DA 36 (039)-85263), December 1959 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, (DA 36 (039)-85263), October 1959 - February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Revised Budget for a $35,000 Increase in the Level of Effort, (DA 36 (039)-85263), March 1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Proposal to Signal Corps for Increase in Scope and Level of Effort, (DA36 (039)-85263), October 1961 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Proposal for an Investigation of Various Topics in Ferrite Nonlinear Travelling Wave Phenomena and Devices, (DA 36 (039)-85263), August 1961 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Proposal to Signal Corps for Extension of Contract for December 1, 1961 through November 30, 1962, (DA 36 (039)-85263), September 1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Proposal to Signal Corps for Extension of Maser Work for December 1, 1959 through November 30, 1961. Proposal submitted as Extention of Contract DA 36 (039)-72785, (DA 36 (039)-85263), August 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Transfer of Plant and Minor Equipment from SEL Contract DA 36 (039) SC-73178, (DA 36 (039)-85263), March 1962 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Property Transfers from DA 36 (039) SC-85, (DA 36 (039)-85263), September 1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Final Property Accounting, (DA 36 (039)-85263), March 1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- SIEGMAN'S CONTRACT ON SOLID STATE OPTICAL MASERS
  - Siegman's Contract, (MW 39 (DA 36 (039) SC 90839)), 1964 - 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Katzman, (MW 39 (DA 36 (039) SC 90839)), January 1963 - January 1964 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Katzman, (MW 39 (DA 36 (039) SC 90839)), April 1962 - December 1962 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- A STUDY OF OPTICAL TRANSITION PROBABILITIES IN SOLIDS AND OF METHODS OF MODULATING THEM
  - Grant Instrument and Research Grant Advice, (DA Grant DA-ARO (D)-31-124-G326), May 1962 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - A Study of Optical Transition Probabilities in Solids and of Methods of Modulating Them, by Schawlow, (DA Grant DA-ARO (D)-31-124-G326), February 1962 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- MILLIMETER GENERATION AND NON-LINEAR PROPAGATION IN FERROMAGNETICS
  - Contract, (DA 36(039) AMC-00041 (E)), September 1962 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, (DA 36(039)AMC-00041 (E)), October 1962 - September 1965 (Box 25, Folder 15)